I need to get through this strong magic region before I run out of mana.
No. Whatever happens, I can't die here.
I have to live long enough to kill him.
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world.
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
To the brand new world.
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world.
Get your hands up, baby!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
Get it on, get it on,始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティー
立ち止まる時間はないさ、Hold on, Hold on!
Now this time, fight for liberty!
真実性、飲み込む常識!
逆境の先にある朝
Oh yeah!
幻想に埋もらえた人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えてもかすぐしていく
Feel it!
We're gonna face!
Let's go!
Leave it myself!
衝動的に突き進め!
Don't be around space!
誰よりも高く飛べ! Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up!
想像せよ偽りのない自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up!
Hey! Yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey! Yeah!
Hey! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Death Mountain
The Giant Traveling Fortress of Condolo created solely for the purpose of crossing the strong magic region.
It sure is coming in handy, huh?
But these people are way too weak. They run out of magic powers so quickly. They're trash.
We just need half of them to live if we want to get through.
Life energy contains mana.
So we'll collect every drop, even from the smallest child.
I realize this summons was abrupt, so thank you for coming.
Don't worry about that, Loro Petchka. Anyway, Spade's forces are drawing closer, aren't they?
Indeed. It won't be long before they make it to the border.
They've done great damage in the last six months. Diamond's essentially been taken over. Both our own nation and the Clover Kingdom currently stand in harm's way.
So in spite of all that preparation we've been doing, they're still one step ahead of us?
Well, I'm ready for a fight whenever.
Good. Then I'd like to send a team to the strong magic region. That's where their forces are now. We can ambush them.
I think timing is going to play a big role here. It might be easier to win if we can draw them in closer to us.
They're crossing a strong magic region, so I'm sure they'll be worn down when they get here. That'll be the time to strike.
Actually, I doubt they'll be weakened by the trip at all. Apparently they're going to arrive in some sort of traveling fortress.
You're kidding me.
The worst part is the way they're abusing the weaker people of their kingdom.
They've been using them as a source of energy.
Asta, hold on!
We're still coming up with a strategy here!
What should we do now? Do you think we should track him down and bring him back?
It's fine. Asta can break through their front lines.
I have confidence in him. He won't be easy for them to defeat.
The only people who would normally be expected to obtain meaningful results from this training are the ones who are loved by mana and experienced higher stage mages.
Asta has no magic at all, and yet he's improved by a surprising amount during the time he spent with us.
It's great that he's at the arcane stage, but I was even more impressed by his hard work and refusal to give up.
Guess that one's done.
So, which one of you chumps wants to go next?
Make sure you carry the fallen to the back.
Sir, I beg you. My sister's so small. Her mana is still weak.
Please, sir, on her limb.
You have some nerve talking out of turn like that.
When you're just a piece of low-stage trash.
Pathetic weaklings like you can't even muster any attack spells.
The only thing you're good for is using your puny magic power to move this fortress around for us.
So if you scum know what's best for you, then you'll do as we say.
If you ask me, you're getting off easy.
I mean, you're not gonna die.
Not till your mana runs out anyway.
Let's see.
I think you'll be the lucky young lady who gets to go next.
No!
You're actually about to be useful for once in your pitiful little life.
You should be happy!
Man, these strong magic regions are something else.
The weather sucks.
I guess I don't have full control over this yet.
Slayer!
You're through!
Given the robe?
I take it that you're a magic knight from Clover.
What are you doing here?
Hmm?
Look at this loser.
He doesn't have any mana.
Pathetic.
And he's here alone?
How stupid can one guy be?
I don't know what you're trying to do, but you're wasting your time.
I'll stop you in your tracks, kid!
Now die!
The only person wasting time here is you.
Even if I'm outnumbered, I'm gonna take every last one of you down.
So you might as well come at me all at once!
You little brats!
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you going to do?
What?
Okay.
I'm Asta from the Clover Kingdom.
I'm a member of the Magic Knights.
Black Bulls.
I came here to help you guys get away.
So don't worry.
You're all safe now.
No, we're doomed.
They were only letting us stay alive.
so that we could fuel this thing.
There's no hope for us.
She's completely terrified.
We can never leave this fortress.
Even if we're set free,
there's no way we could escape the strong magic region with our lives.
Why is this happening?
None of us ever wanted our kingdom to be part of this war.
These poor people.
Now where's the jerk who's making them suffer?
The captain who's in charge of this fortress has a bizarre power.
It's something strange.
As if it's from a different world.
Right.
I'm gonna go beat up every bad guy on this thing,
so you won't have to be afraid.
What? But that's impossible!
Who knows how many soldiers they might have on board!
It's okay!
There's the intruder!
We'll stop you!
Dweller, down!
Black, slack!
Up there.
What the?
Your return!
What?
Who the hell is this guy?
Let's see. It must be there.
You just had to show up here and make a mess of things, didn't you?
From the looks of you, I assume you also have the power of a devil.
Your people are terrified. How could you torture them like this?
Torture them? Not at all.
They're sacrificing themselves in service.
They're nothing but trash, so this is the best fate they could have asked for.
Your people are not trash!
My body!
I don't know how Monolith's filth like you managed to get your pitiful hands on the devil's power,
but you will not be able to evade my technique.
You're no match for a higher-level mage such as myself.
Poison creation magic.
Basilisk breath.
You're worthless.
You won't even make suitable food for this creature.
Destroyer!
What? No. How?
He erased the poison?
How could a worm like him be so strong?
You may have a devil's power,
but it looks like you've only got a tiny piece of it.
Sacrificing your people to help your kingdom?
That's bull.
If you want to fight so badly,
I'll give you all the fight you want!
He's making a mess as usual.
That idiot.
How the heck did he do that?
Alright, I took care of the big guy.
And I wiped out his little buddies, too.
You're all safe now.
I don't believe it.
Seriously?
Hey, look who's here!
Man, Noelle's water armor is so cool.
And now she can use that bubble thing at the same time?
She's gotten way stronger!
Look, just for the record,
using a transport spell while moving through a strong magic region is really difficult.
We realize that, Noelle.
Thanks for getting everyone here safely.
You did a wonderful job.
Truly, it was quite impressive.
Hey, don't patronize me.
I'm royalty, you know.
Uh, yeah, so am I.
What's the big idea, stupid?
Who said you could go barreling out of that meeting and leave us in the dust like that?
I mean, that's pretty typical for him.
You could have at least taken me along with you.
Wow, the excitement of being with Noelle and Mimosa almost killed me.
Wait, no it didn't.
I wasn't excited at all.
Lady Finnis is the only woman who does that for me now.
Oh my, are you all right, miss?
You look like you're distressed.
I only hope you'll allow me to comfort you.
Ugh, stop it!
No comforting other ladies!
Oh, look, sis.
That man's kind of scary.
You've improved a lot too, Finral!
I'm so proud of you!
Thanks a lot.
I'm doing my best.
No way.
Why would you be proud of this loser?
Huh?
I still can't believe there's a woman out there who actually agreed to marry you, Finral.
Are you sure that you didn't just imagine her?
I told you she's real!
Quit asking!
Where'd that come from?
What's happening now?
I can't replenish your mana, but I can heal you at least.
Plant recovery magic.
Princess healing flower paradise.
Awesome!
You've gotten way better at using your magic too, Mimosa!
Seriously cool!
That means a lot, Asta.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
Sounds better.
But still.
The place that all of you came from, it was taken over?
That's right.
Our village was attacked.
One night, the army suddenly showed up with no warning at all.
Anyone who defied them was killed on the spot.
If we tried to go back, they'd probably execute us for escaping.
There's no need to worry.
No need?
We'll fix this.
Our friends are on their way there.
Running off without a plan?
That moron!
We should follow Asta's lead.
Yeah, no way am I gonna let him get all the action!
She's not very regal.
Then again, she is in PJs.
No.
I'd rather you not follow him.
I have a different job for you two.
This is our chance.
I want you to help me take over the Spade Kingdom's outlying base.
Now, Finral, Noelle, and Mimosa, please go and provide backup for Asta.
Um, sorry.
It's just, I'm not sure it's a good idea to split us up.
It'll be all right.
You've all trained hard.
You can do this.
Man, this is such a waste of time.
Why did we have to get stuck watching over this stupid village?
Hey, keep your voice down, would you?
If the captain hears you, we'll all be screwed.
An intruder!
Shoot!
I was told they were all stage two or weaker.
So no matter how many there are, we're sure to win!
Blade Magic Profound Spiral Flames!
No way!
Is it over already?
I guess so.
Sorry there's no one left for you to beat up.
Boo.
Okay, we're all done over here.
That fast?
What's the matter, Asta?
Did you think you were going to hog all the glory?
Keep dreaming.
Holy crap, Leo.
Looks like you got a lot taller.
Well, duh.
Look who my brother and sister are.
Awesome is just in my genes.
So lucky!
I'm gonna head out now.
I marked this place, so I'll be back soon.
Thanks for the help, Finral.
See you then!
Seems everything went well.
We just received word that they were successful in taking control of the base.
And they did even better than I could have expected.
That was impressive.
True, but still.
Yes, I know.
The real battle has yet to begin.
Is the fighting over?
Can we leave now?
Are the soldiers all gone?
We're saved.
What about our village?
What will you do to it?
Huh?
What do you mean, do?
I mean, the ones who just seized control, they're all with you, aren't they?
And you came here from the Clover Kingdom.
We have to obey the strong if we want to survive.
That's the way things work, isn't it?
Oh, we won't do anything.
That's your village.
Do what you want with it.
Our friend, Finral, he's going to make sure everyone gets back safely, so hang tight.
Wow, really?
We're free.
And they won't take Armana?
Thank goodness.
We're so grateful, sir.
Yeah, thanks for being so nice.
No problem.
We just want to stop the devil that's hiding in the Spade Kingdom.
The devil?
Oh, well, you see, as it stands right now, our nation is governed by the Dark Triad, and
they've bestowed power upon another group below them called the Dark Disciples.
Believe me, sir, they're extremely strong.
Rumor has it the Dark Triad are every bit as fearsome as devils themselves.
Oh, man.
That sounds bad.
It appears as though you've gotten quite comfortable with wielding the devil's power,
Xenob.
Yes.
Mostly.
We've received reports that our outlying base has fallen.
The same happened to Kondalo, the mobile fortress we sent toward the Heart Kingdom.
Let's not worry about that.
Our soldiers need something to keep them occupied anyway.
Dante, what's the deal?
Why does Xenon get all the fun?
You let him go to Diamond all by himself, too.
Because I was better suited for that assignment.
So?
What's your point?
You only used about 40% of your power that time.
I'm capable of the exact same thing, thank you very much.
Come on, guys.
When are you going to let me do something interesting?
You have improved quite a bit, Vanica.
That's right.
So let me prove it.
Yes.
You are ready.
And it's time to make our move.
Yay!
Finally!
I get to eat my treat.
I've been saving that thing for so long.
But no more.
So why did we wait for half a year?
We needed to be fully prepared for the events to come.
After all, what would be the fun in letting the game end swiftly?
We're going to wipe out this entire world.
All sense of order.
Mankind's successes.
Nature's beauty.
Everything will be meaningless.
The keys we need to open the door are well within our reach.
You mean the arcane stage mages?
There is no possible salvation for them now.
At this point, we hold existence itself in the palms of our hands.
Ostazov in another land doing his best.
What'd he say?
I think the big battle's going to start soon.
Oh my, it's getting cloudy.
Sir, what happened?
Please, Lord Yuno.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Beautiful, beautiful.
夜明け前の空
静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
Outro Music
To fly
Beautiful
どんな景色も
君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
And never let go
僕のこの手を
離さないでどこまでも
君といってきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
Clover Clips
Comparing Heights
Check it, Asta!
I've really grown a lot lately!
Yeah, it's great and all,
But I feel like I might have grown a little bit too
If you look at me super close!
We're pretty much the same height now,
So there's no reason to brag about stuff like that!
Come on, that's ridiculous!
Let's compare, shall we?
See?
I'm taller!
Asta needs me to help him!
I know just what to do!
There we go!
We're basically the same size now!
How did you do that?
I'm glad I could make him happy!
While I'm at it,why stop at a tie, right?
Eat that,Leo!
Now I'm way taller than you'll ever be!
At first I thought you had been eating your veggies,
But turns out you're just standing on them!
Oopsie daisy!
Leo!
Who said you could grow without me?
It has been six months!
I've also grown a lot!
Hey!
My eyes are up here, buddy!
Black Clover, page 159.
Quiet Lakes and Forest Shadows
And the sweater
krijgen
heat like four days!
And the sweater
is